One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
I grabbed hold, digging in my claws
te ni totte tsume o tateta
but the future
sono mirai wa
blurred together, colors running
nijimu iro ni kasunde mieta
A red that can swallow even summer's hues
natsu no iro mo nuritsubusu you na aka ni
bokura no koe kakikesareteiku you de
now attempts to blot out our voices
Move those halting feet of yours
tachidomaru sono ashi o fumidasou ze
Don't let stand the lies for show
misekake no uso yarisugosu yori
I'll give up countless mornings for my vows
nandome no asa chikai to hikikaeru yo
For the dream that we shared
bokura ga miteita yume
The Height of Folly
"JUSTICE"
Labophase
Back
entrance
Northeast
coast
Egghead
Beep-bup-beep, bup-bip-bop, beep-bup-beep, bup-bip-bop
Piipapii papipo, piipapii papipo piipapii papipo, piipapii
Beep-bup-beep, bup-bip-bop beep-beep-beep-bup-bop
Piipapii papipo, piipapii papipo piipii pipopii, pipopiipii
Beep-bup-beep, bup-bip-bop, beep-bup-beep, bup-bip-bop
Piipapii papipo, piipapii papipo piipapii papipo, piipapii
Beep-bup-beep
Piipapii papipo, piipapii
No No No No No norenai
No, no, no, no, no, not feelin' it
kobiritsuichatte mou odorenai
I'm all stiff, all outta dances
My head feels so good, 'f I get unlucky again
atama Feel so good, mata Unlucky demo
Cola de fukitobase yowaki o
just gonna blow away the shy with a cola
Hey all you boys & girls! Looking good!
soko no Boys & Girls! omae ii yatsu
Hey all you boys & girls!
soko no Boys & Girls!
Update failed. I've had enough!
appudeto wa shippai kori gori
Wasn't it OK 'til yesterday?
kinou made nara seikai?
La la la la la la, run, run, run...
ran ran ran ran ran ran Run Run Run
"Hiding yet?"
mou ii kai?
You ready yet, up for a dance
junbi wa douyo odoreru no?
bukkowareteru kono jidai
in this broken era?
"Come find us!"
mou ii yo!
Spread out from here, drop into the world
koko kara kakusan sekai e Drop
Let loose on the stage of freedom and liberation
jiyuu to kaihou no Stage e
Those rising heads're punks!!!!!! No way!!!
wakiagaru atama ga Punk!!!!!! No way!!!
Sick of waitin', goof off and dance
matenaiyo fuzaketa Dance
Dopamine spilling over
afuredasu dopamin
The lonely singing in unity
kodoku ga tsudoi utau koushin
Bip-bip-bip-bup-bup-bup-bup-bupping
pipipi papapapapatteru
Can't can't can't count me out yet
mada mada mada horobinai
There's some stranger waving me over
shiranai dareka ga temaneki da
Smilin' so wide that it can't be real
uso mitai ni waratteru